[ti:Beat it]
[ar:Michael Jackson]
[al:Beatit]
[by:Kite]
[00:15]BEAT IT
[00:38]They Told Him Don't You Ever Come Around Here
[00:42]Don't Wanna See Your Face, You Better Disappear
[00:45]The Fire's In Their Eyes And Their Words Are Really Clear
[00:48]So Beat It, Just Beat It
[00:53]You Better Run, You Better Do What You Can
[00:55]Don't Wanna See No Blood, Don't Be A Macho Man
[00:59]You Wanna Be Tough, Better Do What You Can
[01:02]So Beat It, But You Wanna Be Bad
[01:07]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[01:09]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[01:13]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[01:15]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[01:20]Just Beat It, Beat It
[01:21]Just Beat It, Beat It
[01:23]Just Beat It, Beat It
[01:25]Just Beat It, Beat It
[01:29]They're Out To Get You, Better Leave While You Can
[01:30]Don't Wanna Be A Boy, You Wanna Be A Man
[01:33]You Wanna Stay Alive, Better Do What You Can
[01:36]So Beat It, Just Beat It
[01:41]You Have To Show Them That You're Really Not Scared
[01:44]You're Playin' With Your Life, This Ain't No Truth Or Dare
[01:47]They'll Kick You, Then They Beat You,
[01:49]Then They'll Tell You It's Fair
[01:50]So Beat It, But You Wanna Be Bad
[01:54]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[01:58]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[02:01]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[02:05]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[02:09]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[02:12]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[02:15]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[02:18]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[02:21]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[02:32]Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[03:21]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[03:25]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[03:28]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[03:31]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[03:34]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[03:38]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[03:41]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Who's Right
[03:45]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[03:49]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[03:52]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[03:55]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[03:59]Just Beat It, Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
[04:02]No One Wants To Be Defeated
[04:05]Showin' How Funky Strong Is Your Fighter
[04:08]It Doesn't Matter Who's Wrong Or Right
[04:09]Just Beat It, Beat It
[04:11]Beat It, Beat It, Beat It
